shoplikeher.com 2017-06-30

# ZEPHYR

### 1\. INTRODUCTION 

Thank you for visiting our privacy policy. We strive to do everything we can to respect the trust users have in our brand and our commitment to your privacy is no exception. We are pleased to provide you with this Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”), which applies to, but not limited to, our search products. Our Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, and safeguard the information that you may provide to us or that we may obtain as our Products are used. Some of the web search services provided herein are provided by and powered by search partners.

### 2\. DATA COLLECTION

The Platform uses cookies, beacons, tags, mobile SDKs, and in some cases non-cookie technologies, to collect Platform Data associated with particular web browsers or devices. We do NOT sell your personal data to third parties. We receive different types of data from our Products listed below, all in anonymous format. We collect these data for debug and user experience improvement purposes.

#### NON-PII

We collect non-PII on our website using cookies, web beacons, and tags for the operation of the site (e.g. managing user sessions), including analyzing site usage, detecting and preventing malicious behavior on the site, and improving the content and organization of the site. We also engage other companies that will use similar methods to collect non-PII on our website for analyzing site usage. We also use non-PII we collect to advertise our business on other sites, including through the Zephyr Platform. When we do so, we act as a customer of the platform, using our own information, and we do not use or mix our information with the proprietary information of other Platform customers. You can learn more about the Zephyr Platform in the Zephyr Platform Privacy page, where you can also learn about how to opt out of having the Platform used by us and others for interest-based advertising.

Platform Data is stored using generally accepted security standards. It is usually aggregated or deleted within 30 days, but may be retained in the Platform for up to 60 days from the date of collection before aggregation or deletion. Aggregated data is used for reporting and analysis, and may be stored in the Platform for up to 12 additional months.

### 3\. INFORMATION 

We will share your personal information only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

From time to time, we may need to disclose your information to third parties such as to law enforcement authorities or our legal advisers, where it is necessary to comply with the law or regulation; enforce or apply our user terms and conditions; to protect our rights, or to preserve the safety of our users. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

We may also share your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities (e.g. processing payments or submitting emails to you on our behalf), in connection with any merger, a sale of Zephyr assets, or a financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. Whenever we share your personal information for this reason we will ensure that the recipient is bound by all appropriate confidentiality obligations and that it commits to using your personal information only for the purposes for which you originally provided it.

You should also be aware that the information submitted to public areas, such as our blogs, may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

If you interact with social media features on our site, such as the Facebook Like button, or use your social network credentials to comment on our blog, these features may collect information about your use of this site as well as post information about your activities on this site to your profile page. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### 4\. COPPA

This site is not intended for, or designed to attract, children. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 13.

### 5\. DATA PROTECTION

When you press the "restore" button in account settings to log into our cloud-based services, your input preferences will be automatically transferred over encrypted channels to our servers. If you are not logged into the cloud-based services, no input preferences will be transferred from your device. Please note that all data transferred between your device and our services is encrypted, including any personal data we may collect on your behalf.

### 6\. CHANGE OF CONTROL

If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of Zephyr Digital or our assets to another organization (e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution or liquidation), data received from or about our users may be among the items sold or transferred. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy Policy.

### 7\. POLICY CHANGES

Zephyr Digital reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time by updating this page. Therefore we encourage you to check this page regularly to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This Privacy Policy was last updated on December 1st, 2016.

### 8\. CONTACT US

Zephyr Digital  
101 California St.   
#2710 San Francisco, CA 94111  
partners@zephyr-digital.com
